Finding Aid for Francis W. Ouradnik photographs, 1928-1968
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Francis W. Ouradnik photographs
1928-1968
Ouradnik, Francis W.
92661 Aa 2
Official photographer for the University Players (formerly Play Production) at the University of Michigan starting in 1928; photographic negatives of cast (in costume) from various student productions.
420 negatives in 2 boxes; number approximate
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was donated in 1978 by Jean Ouradnik Zearley (donor 6186 ). Additional material was donated by Constance L. Jones (donor 9380 ) in 2013.
The collection is open to research.
Francis W. Ouradnik served as official photographer for the University Players (formerly Play Production) at the University of Michigan starting in 1928. He was the only professional photographer to serve the organization, although various amateurs and semi-professionals have also contributed to the University Players. Ouradnik continued in the role of photographer until his death in 1968. Ouradnik photographed each production after the Thursday night performance, usually taking fourteen photos of poses arranged by the director of the play. The purpose of his photographs were both as a record of the production and because of the requests made for copies from the student players.
The Francis W. Ouradnik collection consists of 421 black and white negatives of scenes from plays produced by the University Players (formerly Play Production) at the University of Michigan in the period of 1928 to 1968. Francis Ouradnik, produced the majority of the negatives. A partial listing of the plays, which he made, can be found with the negatives.
The collection has been arranged into three series: two series of negatives and a series containing positive photographs. The first series contains photographic negatives dated from 1928 to 1944 (32 photos), apparently not taken by Ouradnik. The second series, running from 1934 to 1968, numbers 389 negatives identified as being taken by Ouradnik. Each series is arranged chronologically with a very few exceptions.
All negatives and photographs are black and white, and only a few scattered copies are not identified by date. Ouradnik composed a list of his negative file of plays and a copy is enclosed with the collection. Only three productions for these years cannot be located. All there are for the year 1947: "In Spite of Heaven," "Candida," and "In the Zone."
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Photography.; Theatrical productions.; University of Michigan--Dramatics.Dramatics.; University of Michigan. Play Production.; University Players (University of Michigan)
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Photographic Negatives, 1928-1944
  - Cassilis Engagement, December 12, 1928 (Box 1)
  - A Little Journey, 1928 (Box 1)
  - Wedding Bells, 1929 (Box 1)
  - The Truth About Blayds, 1929 (Box 1)
  - Children Of The Moon, 1929 (Box 1)
  - Redemption, 1929 (Box 1)
  - Donphey Dell, 1930 (Box 1)
  - Marriage Of Convenience, 1931 (Box 1)
  - Scrambled Ego, 1931 (Box 1)
  - Paris Bound, 1931 (Box 1)
  - Tour De Monde, August 10, 1932 (Box 1)
  - Chalk Circle, 1932 (Box 1)
  - Hedda Gabler, 1933 (Box 1)
  - Journey's End, 1933 (Box 1)
  - Hay Fever, 1933 (Box 1)
  - Autumn Crocus, 1933 (Box 1)
  - The Round Table, 1933 (Box 1)
  - Dance Program-Political Meeting, 1934 (Box 1)
  - See Naples and Die, 1934 (Box 1)
  - Midsummer [?], 1935 (Box 1)
  - Midsummer Night's Dream, 1935 (Box 1)
  - Twelfth Night, 1935 (Box 1)
  - Kingdom Of God, 1935 (Box 1)
  - Good Old Summertime, 1936 (Box 1)
  - Ruddigore, 1936 (Box 1)
  - Robin Hood, 1936 (Box 1)
  - Mary Of Scot, 1936 (Box 1)
  - Mr. Toad, November, 1937 (Box 1)
  - Yeoman Of The Guards, 1937 (Box 1)
  - Pirates Of Penzance, June 12, 1938 (Box 1)
  - Henry VIII, 1938 (Box 1)
  - Washington Slept Here, July 8, 1941 (Box 1)
  - Phillipi, May, 1944 (Box 1)
- Photographic Negatives, 1934-1968
  - 1934
    - Double Door, 1934 (Box 1)
    - Both Your Houses, July 13, 1934 (Box 1)
    - Marco Millions, August 9, 1934 (Box 1)
    - Cradle Song, August 14, 1934 (Box 1)
  - 1935
    - Doctor Knock, March 7, 1935 (Box 1)
    - Othello, July 24, 1935 (Box 1)
    - Doctor By Pressure, July 31, 1935 (Box 1)
    - Chocolate Soldier, August 8, 1935 (Box 1)
  - 1936
    - The Pigeon, August, 1936 (Box 1)
    - The Old Maid, August, 1936 (Box 1)
  - 1937
    - Path Of Flowers, 1937 (Box 1)
    - Daughters Of Atreus, 1937 (Box 1)
    - Bartered Bride, June 17, 1937 (Box 1)
    - Yellow Jack, July 1, 1937 (Box 1)
    - Pride & Prejudice, July 8, 1937 (Box 1)
    - Ethan Frome, July, 1937 (Box 1)
    - First Lady, July 15, 1937 (Box 1)
    - Accent On Youth, August 6, 1937 (Box 1)
    - Pinafore, August 14, 1937 (Box 1)
    - Excursion, October 30, 1937 (Box 1)
  - 1938
    - Proud Pilgrimage, January 20, 1938 (Box 1)
    - High Tor, March 31, 1938 (Box 1)
    - Shoemaker's Holiday, April, 1938 (Box 1)
    - Kind Lady, June, 1938 (Box 1)
    - Arms and The Man, July 10, 1938 (Box 1)
    - Androcles and the Lion, 1938 (Box 1)
    - Brother Rat, 1938 (Box 1)
    - Idiot's Delight, July 21, 1938 (Box 1)
    - Whiteheaded Boy, July, 1938 (Box 1)
    - Vagabond King, August, 1938 (Box 1)
  - 1939
    - Two Gentlemen From Verona, May, 1939 (Box 1)
    - Our Town, July 20, 1939 (Box 1)
    - Judgment Day, August 4, 1939 (Box 1)
    - Michael and Mary, August, 1939 (Box 1)
    - Iolanthe, August 15, 1939 (Box 1)
    - Good Hope, August 29, 1939 (Box 1)
    - Family Portrait, November 1, 1939 (Box 1)
    - Children's Plays, December 1, 1939 (Box 1)
    - Third Of A Nation, December 7, 1939 (Box 1)
  - 1940
    - Julius Caesar, February 24, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Il Seraglio, March 7, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Critic, March 28, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Two On An Is, April 18, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Winters Tale, May 20, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Boyd's Shop, June 9, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Guardsmen, June 14, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Star Wagon, July 4, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Beyond The Horizon, July 11, 1940 (Box 1)
    - What A Life, July 25, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Escape, August 2, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Patience, August 9, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Three Men On A Horse, November 1, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Bat, November 15, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Margin For Error, December 9, 1940 (Box 1)
  - 1941
    - Trelawney Of The Wells, February 28, 1941 (Box 1)
    - Success, March 7, 1941 (Box 1)
    - Much Ado About Nothing, March 21, 1941 (Box 1)
    - Remember The Day, April 4, 1941 (Box 1)
    - Washington Slept Here, July 11, 1941 (Box 1)
    - Contrast, July 19, 1941 (Box 1)
    - Little Foxes, July 25, 1941 (Box 1)
    - Storm Over Patsy, August 1, 1941 (Box 1)
    - Hobson's Choice, August 8, 1941 (Box 1)
    - Gondoliers, August 14, 1941 (Box 1)
    - Holy Plays, August 18, 1941 (Box 1)
    - Jim Dandy, November 7, 1941 (Box 1)
    - Bluebird, December 5, 1941 (Box 1)
  - 1942
    - Impresario and Cavalleria Rusticana, March 5, 1942 (Box 1)
    - Under The Gaslight, April 3, 1942 (Box 1)
    - Rivals, July 9, 1942 (Box 1)
    - Thunderrock, July 16, 1942 (Box 1)
    - Hay Fever, July 24, 1942 (Box 1)
    - Letters To Luanne, July 31, 1942 (Box 1)
    - Misalliance, August 7, 1942 (Box 1)
    - Pinafore, August 14, 1942 (Box 1)
  - 1943
    - Caste, April 3, 1943 (Box 1)
    - The Wishful Taw, May 13, 1943 (Box 1)
    - Ladies In Retirement, July 9, 1943 (Box 1)
    - Alice Sit By The Fire, July 15, 1943 (Box 1)
    - Little, July 29, 1943 (Box 1)
    - Papa Is All, August 6, 1943 (Box 1)
    - Hansel and Gretel, August 12, 1943 (Box 1)
    - [Special For Music], December, 1943; 2 envelopes (Box 1)
  - 1944
    - Mr. Dooley, January 27, 1944 (Box 1)
    - Comedy Of Errors, February 10, 1944 (Box 1)
    - She Stoops To Conquer, Spring 1944 (Box 1)
    - Little Women, Spring 1944 (Box 1)
    - Streets Of New York, May 8, 1944 (Box 1)
    - Damask Cheek, July 13, 1944 (Box 1)
    - Learned Ladies, July 20, 1944 (Box 1)
    - Journey To Jerusalem, August 3, 1944 (Box 1)
    - Chocolate Soldier, August 18, 1944 (Box 1)
    - Junior Miss, December 14, 1944 (Box 1)
  - 1945
    - Tim Soldier, January 18, 1945 (Box 1)
    - Skin Of Our Teeth, February 8, 1945 (Box 1)
    - Uncle Harry, April 12, 1945 (Box 1)
    - Shoemaker, May 10, 1945 (Box 1)
    - Tonight At 8:30, June 7, 1945 (Box 1)
    - Blythe Spirit, July 12, 1945 (Box 1)
    - Male Animal, July 19, 1945 (Box 1)
    - Quality Street, August 2, 1945 (Box 1)
    - Over 21, August 9, 1945 (Box 1)
    - Naughty Marietta, August 16, 1945 (Box 1)
    - What A Life, December 14, 1945 (Box 1)
  - 1946
    - The Maid and The Thief, January 17, 1946 (Box 1)
    - Beggars On Horseback, February 7, 1946 (Box 1)
    - Kind Lady, April 11, 1946 (Box 1)
    - Camel With The Wrinkled Knees, May 10, 1946 (Box 1)
    - The Devil's Disciple, June 6, 1946 (Box 1)
    - Papa Is All, July 11, 1946 (Box 1)
    - Pigeons and People, July 18, 1946 (Box 1)
    - Angell Street, August 1, 1946 (Box 1)
    - Apple Cart, August 8, 1946 (Box 1)
    - The Bartered Bride, August 15, 1946 (Box 1)
    - The Late Christopher Bean, August 21, 1946 (Box 1)
    - Both Your Houses, November 1, 1946 (Box 1)
    - Aladdin and His Lamp, November 22, 1946 (Box 1)
  - 1947
    - In The Zone, January 14, 1947 (Box 1)
    - The Truth, January 17, 1947 (Box 1)
    - Marriage Of Figaro, March 13, 1947 (Box 1)
    - Saint Joan, April 25, 1947 (Box 1)
    - In Spite Of Heaven, May 22, 1947 (Box 1)
    - Candida, July 3, 1947 (Box 1)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace, July 10, 1947 (Box 1)
    - The Kings' Henchmen, July 18, 1947 (Box 1)
    - Last Stop, July 24, 1947 (Box 1)
    - Temper The Wind, August 1, 1947 (Box 1)
    - Carmen, August 8, 1947 (Box 1)
    - Our Town, November 6, 1947 (Box 1)
    - Radio Rescue, November 24, 1947 (Box 1)
  - 1948
    - As We Like It, January 15, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Dido and Athenus, March 11, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Telephone, March 11, 1948 (Box 1)
    - The Importance Of Being Earnest, April 22, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Berkeley Square, May 20, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Of Thee I Sing, July 1, 1948 (Box 1)
    - The Late George Apley, July 8, 1948 (Box 1)
    - You Can't Take It With You, July 15, 1948 (Box 1)
    - I Remember 14ama, July 29, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Down In The Valley and La Serva Patrama (?), August 5, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Summer Solstice, October 28, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Emperor's New Clothes, December 1, 1948 (Box 1)
  - 1949
    - Dr. Faustus, January 13, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Sister Angelica and Giami Schicchi, March 10, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Tovarich, March 24, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Abe Lincoln In Illinois, April 28, 1949 (Box 1)
    - On Borrowed Time, June 30, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Life With Father, July 7, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Glass Menagerie, July 14, 1949 (Box 1)
    - White Speed, July 21, 1949 (Box 1)
    - The Trojan Women, July 28, 1949 (Box 1)
    - La Bohme, August 4, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Servant Of Two Masters, October 27, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Family Portrait, December 1, 1949 (Box 1)
  - 1950
    - The Traitor, January 12, 1950 (Box 1)
    - Cosi Fan Tutte, March 9, 1950 (Box 1)
    - King Lear, March 30, 1950 (Box 1)
    - School For Husbands, April 27, 1950 (Box 1)
    - The Corn Is Green, July 6, 1950 (Box 1)
    - Antigone, July 13, 1950 (Box 1)
    - Time Of Your Life, July 20, 1950 (Box 1)
    - Hansel and Gretel, August 3, 1950 (Box 1)
    - The Great Adventure, August 10, 1950 (Box 1)
    - Midsummer's Night Dream, November 3, 1950 (Box 1)
    - Caesar and Cleopatra, November 30, 1950 (Box 1)
  - 1951
    - Command Decision, January 18, 1951 (Box 1)
    - The Magic Flute, March 8, 1951 (Box 1)
    - Romeo and Juliet, March 29, 1951 (Box 1)
    - One Act Plays, April 26, 1951 (Box 1)
    - Green Grows The Lilacs, July 5, 1951 (Box 1)
    - An Enemy Of The People, July 12, 1951 (Box 1)
    - The Enchanted, July 26, 1951 (Box 1)
    - The Streets Of New York, August 2, 1951 (Box 1)
    - The Chocolate Soldier, August 9, 1951 (Box 1)
    - Live On Air, November 2, 1951 (Box 1)
    - King Richard II, November 29, 1951 (Box 1)
  - 1952
    - The Fan, January 18, 1952 (Box 1)
    - Don Giovanni, March 6, 1952 (Box 1)
    - There Shall Be No Night, March 28, 1952 (Box 1)
    - [Miscellaneous], April 2, 1952 (Box 1)
    - Once In A Lifetime, April 25, 1952 (Box 1)
      (include contact print)
    - Twelfth Night, July 3, 1952 (Box 1)
    - Harvey, July 11, 1952 (Box 1)
    - Mrs. McThing, July 22, 1952 (Box 1)
    - Winterset, July 25, 1952 (Box 1)
    - Second Threshold, August 1, 1952 (Box 1)
    - The Merry Wives Of Windsor, August 8, 1952 (Box 1)
    - The Shadow and The Rock, October 31, 1952 (Box 1)
    - The Birds, December 13, 1952 (Box 1)
  - 1953
    - Faust, February 28, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Right You Are If You Think You Are, March 23, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Madame Butterfly, April 23, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Deep Are The Roots, April 24, 1953 (Box 1)
    - The Mad Woman Of Chaillot, July 2, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Knickerbocker Holiday, July 9, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Country Girl, July 23, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Pygmalion, July 30, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Tales Of Hoffman, August 7, 1953 (Box 1)
    - The Heiress, October 29, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Elizabeth The Queen, November 14, 1953 (Box 1)
  - 1954
    - Tartuffe, January 15, 1954 (Box 1)
    - Ariadne Of Naxos, March 3, 1954 (Box 1)
    - Taming Of The Shrew, March 26, 1954 (Box 1)
    - Veranda On The Highway, April 23, 1954 (Box 1)
    - Hamlet, July 8, 1954 (Box 1)
    - The Critic, July 29, 1954 (Box 1)
    - The Marriage Of Figaro, August 6, 1954 (Box 1)
    - Dream Girl, December 9, 1954 (Box 1)
  - 1955
    - She Stoops To Conquer, January 1, 1955 (Box 1)
    - [A Greek Play], January 15, 1955 (Box 1)
    - Falstaff, March 2, 1955 (Box 1)
    - The Skin Of Our Teeth, March 24, 1955 (Box 1)
    - The Clugstone Inheritance, April 29, 1955 (Box 1)
    - Ring Around The Moon, July 1, 1955 (Box 1)
    - Bell, Book, and Candle, July 7, 1955 (Box 1)
    - The Happy Time, July 20, 1955 (Box 1)
    - Heartbreak House, July 22, 1955 (Box 1)
    - Fidelio, August 5, 1955 (Box 1)
    - The Good Woman Of Setzuan, November 11, 1955 (Box 1)
    - The Worlds Of Tommy Albright, December 9, 1955 (Box 1)
  - 1956
    - Magic Flute, March 7, 1956 (Box 1)
    - My Very Own, March 29, 1956 (Box 1)
    - Misanthrope, April 27, 1956 (Box 1)
    - Anastasia, July 5, 1956 (Box 1)
    - The Circle, July 13, 1956 (Box 1)
    - The Wayward Saint, July 26, 1956 (Box 1)
    - The Lady's Not For Burning, August 21, 1956 (Box 1)
    - La Bohme, August 10, 1956 (Box 1)
    - Under The Gaslight, November 2, 1956 (Box 1)
    - Hansel and Gretel, December 7, 1956 (Box 1)
    - Juno and The Peacock, December 14, 1956 (Box 1)
  - 1957
    - Cavalleria Rusticana and The Fair, March 8, 1957 (Box 1)
    - The Burning Ground, March 29, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Man In Armour, March 29, 1957 (Box 1)
    - The Tragedy Of Richard III, April 26, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Charlie's Aunt, July 3, 1957 (Box 1)
    - School For Wives, July 10, 1957 (Box 1)
    - The Desperate Hours, July 24, 1957 (Box 1)
    - The Chalk Circle, July 31, 1957 (Box 1)
    - The Bartered Bride, August 8, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace, November 8, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Desire Under The Elms, December 12, 1957 (Box 1)
    - And We Have All The Fun, December 13, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Alice In Wonder, Undated (Box 1)
    - Waiting For Lefty, Undated (Box 1)
  - 1958
    - A Masked Ball, February 28, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Playboy Of The Western World, March 21, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Love's Lost Labor, April 25, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Inherit The Wind, July 10, 1958 (Box 2)
    - The Potting Shed, July 17, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Philadelphia Story, July 31, 1958 (Box 2)
    - La Traviata, August 8, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Ah Wilderness, November 7, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Matchmaker, December 12, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Cosi Fan Tutte, December 15, 1958 (Box 2)
  - 1959
    - Barber Of Seville, February 26, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Valpone, April 10, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Electra, April 27, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Man On A Tiger, May 15, 1959 (Box 2)
    - The Boyfriend, June 26, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Look Back In Anger, July 10, 1959 (Box 2)
    - The Rivals, July 17, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Waltz Of The Toreadors, July 31, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Rigoletto, August 7, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Knock At The Door, October 16, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Horse Eat Hat, October 30, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Don Pasquale, November 19, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Epitaph For George Dillon, December 11, 1959 (Box 2)
  - 1960
    - Das Reingold, March 2, 1960 (Box 2)
    - The Way Of The World, April 7, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Look Forward Anger, April 28, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Journey To A Distant Point, May 13, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Annie Get Your Gun, June 23, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Amphitryon 38, July 7, 1960 (Box 2)
    - As You Like It, July 21, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Picnic, July 28, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Don Giovanni, August 4, 1960 (Box 2)
    - First Born, October 20, 1960 (Box 2)
    - The Frog, November 4, 1960 (Box 2)
    - [Three Opera Sketches], November 17, 1960
      - Hansel and Gretel (Box 2)
      - Paliacci (Box 2)
      - Flying Dutchman (Box 2)
    - Purple Dust, December 9, 1960 (Box 2)
  - 1961
    - Season Of The Beast, January 12, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Pelleas and Melisande, March 8, 1961 (Box 2)
    - School For Husbands, April 13, 1961 (Box 2)
    - The Visit, April 27, 1961 (Box 2)
    - J.B., June 29, 1961 (Box 2)
    - My Three Angels, July 13, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Bed Bug, July 20, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Rashomon, August 3, 1961 (Box 2)
    - The Marriage Of Figaro, August 10, 1961 (Box 2)
    - The Trial, October 26, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Arms and The Man, November 9, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Henry IV (Part I), December 7, 1961 (Box 2)
  - 1962
    - Faces Of Malite, January 11, 1962 (Box 2)
    - [Dance Review], March 15, 1962 (Box 2)
    - The Living Room, March 22, 1962 (Box 2)
    - The Merry Wives Of Windsor, April 30, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Henry IV (Part 2), May 9, 1962 (Box 2)
    - The Boys From Syracuse, June 28, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Five Finger Exercise, July 12, 1962 (Box 2)
    - The Queen and the Rebels, July 19, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Under Milk Wood, August 2, 1962 (Box 2)
    - La Serva Padrona and Gianni Schicchi, August 9, 1962 (Box 2)
    - The Servant Of Two Masters, November 1, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Carmen, December 6, 1962 (Box 2)
  - 1963
    - Six Characters In Search Of An Author, January 10, 1963 (Box 2)
    - The Hunters, March 7, 1963 (Box 2)
    - The House Of Bernard Alba, March 28, 1963 (Box 2)
    - The Madwoman Of Chaillot, April 25, 1963 (Box 2)
    - A Matter Of Style, May 16, 1963 (Box 2)
    - South Pacific, June 27, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Two For The Seesaw, July 11, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Androcles and the Lion, July 18, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Monique, August 1, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Madame Butterfly, August 8, 1963 (Box 2)
    - The Miser, October 17, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Thieves Carnival, November 14, 1963 (Box 2)
    - The Importance Of Being Earnest, December 5, 1963 (Box 2)
  - 1964
    - The Firebug, February 24, 1964 (Box 2)
    - The Tiger and Shanakind, April 2, 1964 (Box 2)
    - King Henry V, April 23, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Queen Of Spades, May 7, 1964 (Box 2)
    - My Fair Lady, June 25, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Summer and Smoke, July 9, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Under The Sycamore Tree, July 16, 1964 (Box 2)
    - A Thurber Carnival, July 30, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Fra Diavalo, August 6, 1964 (Box 2)
    - Gideon, October 8, 1964 (Box 2)
    - The Emperor's New Clothes, October 24, 1964 (Box 2)
    - The Imaginary Invalid, November 5, 1964 (Box 2)
    - The Peacemaker, December 3, 1964 (Box 2)
  - 1965
    - Uncle Vanya, January 1965 (Box 2)
    - Chez Torpe, February 18, 1965 (Box 2)
    - King Midas and The Golden Touch, February 27, 1965 (Box 2)
    - The Magic Flute, March 18, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Galileo, April 8, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Antigone, June 11, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Bedtime Story, June11, 1965 (Box 2)
    - The Bald Soprano, June11, 1965 (Box 2)
    - He Three Penny Opera, July 1, 1965 (Box 2)
    - The Confidential Clerk, July 15, 1965 (Box 2)
    - The Private Ear and The Public Eye, July 22, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Pied Piper Of Hamelin, July 29, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Measure For Measure, August 5, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Hansel and Gretel, August 12, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Mr. Popper's Penguins, October 2, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Henry VI (Part I), November 18, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Henry VI (Part 2), November 20, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Henry VI (Part 3), November 23, 1965 (Box 2)
  - 1966
    - The Days Between, February 3, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Cassandra, February 17, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Pierre Pathelin, February 26, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Rosalinda, March 17, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Peer Gynt, April 7, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Misalliance, June 2, 1966 (Box 2)
    - The Winter's Tale, June 30, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Enrico IV, July 14, 1966 (Box 2)
    - The Birthday Party, July 21, 1966 (Box 2)
    - The Reluctant Doctor, July 28, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Blithe Spirit, August 4, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Cosi Fan Tutte, August 11, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Coriolanus, October 13, 1966 (Box 2)
    - The Thirteen Clocks, October 29, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Cowboy In Absentia, November 10, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Camino Real, December 1, 1966 (Box 2)
  - 1967
    - Incident At Vichy, February 9, 1967 (Box 2)
    - The Magic Horn, February 18, 1967 (Box 2)
    - After The Fall, March 16, 1967 (Box 2)
    - The Crucible, April 6, 1967 (Box 2)
    - The Playboy Of The Western World, June 1, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Nobody Loves A Dragon, June 10, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Macbeth, June 29, 1967 (Box 2)
    - The Physicists, July 13, 1967 (Box 2)
    - The Country Wife, July 27, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Little Merry Sunshine, August 10, 1967 (Box 2)
    - King John, October 5, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Cinderella, October 21, 1967 (Box 2)
    - Sergeant Musgrave's Dance, November 2, 1967 (Box 2)
    - The Would-Be Gentleman, November 30, 1967 (Box 2)
  - 1968
    - The Ghose Sonata and The Stronger, February 8, 1968 (Box 2)
    - The Elves and The Shoemaker, February 27, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Jude, March 14, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Antigone, April 4, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Reynard The Fox, May 25, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Major Barbara, June 6, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Troilus and Cressida, June 27, 1968 (Box 2)
    - The Burnt Flower-Bed, July 11, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Hotel Paradiso, July 25, 1968 (Box 2)
    - The Alchemist, August 8, 1968 (Box 2)
- Photographic Positives
  - July 25, 1940 (Box 2)
  - August 6, 1940 (Box 2)
  - Undated (Box 2)